Okay, so I'm gonna play this first video, and then I'm gonna play a second video, and
you do the math.
Alright, so now I'm gonna play the second video.
Well, Israel is a law that says if an Israeli marries a Palestinian, or someone from several
other regional Arab states, that person isn't allowed to move in with said Israeli.
This law was passed in 2003, but it's been renewed every single year since.
Israel also doesn't allow interreligious marriage to be performed in the country, which is meant
to deter Jews from marrying non-Jews.
In 2018, Israel passed the Nation-State Law, a law which has constitutional status, which
says the right to exercise national self-determination, i.e. have rights, is the exclusive right of
Jews, no one else.
There's also the Nakba Law, which makes it illegal to acknowledge the Nakba, the expulsions
of Palestinians that were needed to found Israel.
This would be like passing a law to make it illegal to talk about indigenous genocide or
slavery in America.
There's also the admissions committee law, which basically allows towns to operate panels
that deny applications for entry based on socio-cultural compatibility, which essentially
just legalizes racist housing discrimination.
In Israel, advocating genocide of Palestinians doesn't hurt your chances of holding a high
position in government.
And in fact, in many cases, it helps.
When they start calling the truth propaganda, boy, that is some proper-ganda.
Don't get rejected.
And after all, let's get rejected.